ILR School Research and Publications Department Files /4011
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Research and Publications Department Files
1947-1960
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
/4011
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3082817
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 21, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations Research and Publications Department; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Administration.
3082817
- Advisory Council 1951-52, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Foundations - Projects 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Foundations - Projects (Prior to 1950) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Graduate Students and Graduate Program 1951 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Graduate Students and Graduate Program 1951 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Graduate Students and Graduate Program (Prior to 1951) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Memos (to and from the Dean) - 1954 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Memos (to and from the Dean) - 1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Memos - 1948 and Prior to (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Memos (Misc.), 1950 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- A, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Annual Report 1949 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Annual Report 1950 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Annual Report 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- C, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Memos to and From the Dean - 1948 and Prior To (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Memos to and From the Dean - 1949 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Dean Catherwood (Memos - To and From), 1950 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Dean Catherwood (Memos-To and From) '51-'52, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- D, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- E, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- G, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- H, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- K, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Mc, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- M, 1948-1950 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- O, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Charles A. Pearce, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- P, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- R, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Research Projects Planned - 1949 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- S, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- T, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- W, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Misc., 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- 1958 - (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Summary, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Social Science Research Center - Minutes, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Social Science Research Council, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- SSRC - Ford Foundation Grant, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Human Relations Research Group (Meetings), 1953 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- ILR Staff Recommendations - Adams, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- SSRC - Memo on University Research Programs, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- SSRC - Committee on Research Training, etc., 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Workshop Units in Social Studies, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Wage Stabilization Data, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Malisoff, Harry Disabled- Handicapped, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Manpower Research Center, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- War Emergency Research, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Vadakin N.Y.S. Disability Benefits Law, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Utica Area Dept. of Labor - Project, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Stuart, Dean Damage Suits, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Social Security Research Report, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Seidenberg, Jacob Injunction Study, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Secondary School Program, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Rosett Material, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Manuscript - Unpublished - "Rehabilitation", 1950 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Puchek, Michael Pension Plans, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Labor Market Research Studies, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Loblaw Groceterias, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Labor-Management Committees, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Memoranda - General, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Edwin E. White, 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Memoranda Dean Catherwood, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Risley's Office, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Editorial Board Minutes of Meetings, etc. Memos, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- First Table of Contents - Review (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Leonard Adams, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- QA Summer H. Slichter, 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- A.W. Rucker, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- George B. Robinson, 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Clarence B. Randall, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Max Nomad, 1947-1950 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- King Macrury, 1949-1951 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- William McPherson, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Norman Maier, 1948-1952 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- David A. Morse, 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- John F. McMahon (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Selig Perlman, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Margaret Cole, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Memoranda - General, 1947-1950 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Lee Eckert, 1947-1950 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Manuscripts found in Folders, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Manuscripts Book Reviews found in old Files, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Manuscripts Book Reviews found in old Files, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 23)